They say they love each other, I know that they do.
他们说他们相爱，我知道他们是真心的。
They say they'll always be together, that may not be true.
他们说他们会永远在一起，但也许不是真的。
They come from different places, different points of view.
他们来自不同的地方，有不同的观点。
They find themselves in different spaces, everything is all brand new.
他们发现自己在不同的空间，一切都是全新的。
Two different directions, too many different ways.
两种不同的方向，太多不同的方式。
One always on the road somewhere, the other one always stays.
一个总是在路上，另一个总是待在原地。
Too often unhappy, too often on your own.
太常不开心，太常独自一人。
When you are moving in different directions, true love is all alone.
当你们朝不同的方向前进，真爱就孤独了。
Old stories start to surface, patterns from long ago.
旧故事开始浮出水面，来自很久以前的模式。
And loving quickly turns to anger, for reasons they don't even know.
而且爱很快变成了愤怒，原因他们甚至不知道。
The strongest heart can be broken with one insensitive word.
最坚强的心也会因一句无情的话而破碎。
The deepest feelings remain unspoken, no one is seen, nothing heard.
最深的感情未曾言说，无人可见，没有声音传出。
Two different directions, too many different ways.
两种不同的方向，太多不同的方式。
One always wants to work things out, the other one wants to play.
一个总是想解决问题，另一个想玩。
Too ready for changes, and too much that just can't wait.
太容易改变，太多事情不能等待。
When you are moving in different directions, true love can turn to hate.
当你们朝不同的方向前进，真爱可以变成憎恨。
If opposites attract each other, what's the reason for?
如果相反的东西相互吸引，原因是什么？
One being like an open window, one just like a closing door.
一个像敞开的窗户，一个就像关闭的门。
Two different directions, too many different ways.
两种不同的方向，太多不同的方式。
One likes to see the morning sunrise, the other one sleeps in bed.
一个喜欢看早晨的日出，另一个睡在床上。
Too many tomorrow, too many times too late.
明天太多，太多次都太迟了。
When you are moving in different directions, true love may have to wait.
当你们朝不同的方向前进，真爱也许必须等待。
If you are committed to different directions, true love will have to wait.
如果你们朝不同的方向承诺，真爱将不得不等待。
Thank you for watching!
谢谢观看！